--Q1:
select lname||', '||fname as Employee_Name, salary as Salary from employee;

--Q2:
select * from employee where commission is null;

--Q3:
select unique building from location;

--Q4:
select * from crssection where termid = (select termid from term where termdesc = 'Winter 2003');

--Q5:
select Name as Faculty_Name from faculty where deptid in (1,2);

--Q6:
select * from student where State in ('NJ','NY');

--Q7:
select salary, salary*1.1 as Raised_Salary from employee where employeeId = 111;
update employee set salary = salary*1.1 where employeeid = 111;
select salary, salary/1.1 as Original_Salary from employee where employeeId = 111;

--Q8:
delete department where deptid = 30;

--correct: ALTER TABLE Employee DROP CONSTRAINT FK_DEPTNO;